{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "How to get a response from an activity in Android?",
      "options": [
        "startActivityToResult",
        "startActivityForResult",
        "Bundle",
        "none of the above"
      ],
      "answer": "startActivityForResult"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is splash screen in android?",
      "options": [
        "initial activity of an application",
        "initial service of an applicaion",
        "initial method of an application",
        "initial screen of an applicaion"
      ],
      "answer": "initial screen of an applicaion"
    },
    {
      "question": "How to stop the services in android?",
      "options": [
        "finish()",
        "system.exit()",
        "by manually",
        "stopSelf and stopService()"
      ],
      "answer": "stopSelf and stopService()"
    },
    {
      "question": "How many applications are there in a given task in android?",
      "options": [
        "Two",
        "One",
        "Many",
        "Zero"
      ],
      "answer": "Many"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which permissions are required to get a location in android?",
      "options": [
        "ACCESS_FINE and ACCESS_COARSE",
        "GPRS",
        "Internet permisson",
        "WIFI permission"
      ],
      "answer": "ACCESS_FINE and ACCESS_COARSE"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is breakpoint in android?",
      "options": [
        "Breaks the applicaion",
        "Breaks the development code",
        "Break the execution",
        "None of the above"
      ],
      "answer": "Break the execution"
    },
    {
      "question": "In which technique, we can refresh the dynamic content in android?",
      "options": [
        "Java",
        "Ajax",
        "Android",
        "None of the above"
      ],
      "answer": "Ajax"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is fragment life cycle in android?",
      "options": [
        "onReceive()",
        "onCreate()",
        "onAttach() -> OnCreate() -> onCreateView() -> onActivityCreated() -> onStart() -> onResume() -> onPause() -> onStop() -> onDestroyView() -> onDestroy() -> onDetach()",
        "None of the above"
      ],
      "answer": "onAttach() -> OnCreate() -> onCreateView() -> onActivityCreated() -> onStart() -> onResume() -> onPause() -> onStop() -> onDestroyView() -> onDestroy() -> onDetach()"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is ANR responding time in android?",
      "options": [
        "10 sec",
        "5 sec",
        "1 min",
        "None of the above"
      ],
      "answer": "5 sec"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a thread in android?",
      "options": [
        "Same as Services",
        "Background activity",
        "Broadcast Receiver",
        "inependent dis-patchable unit is called a thread"
      ],
      "answer": "inependent dis-patchable unit is called a thread"
    }
  ]
}